<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>people on Intro COS Lab</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/blog/people/</link><description>Recent content in people on Intro COS Lab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2022, Department of Computer Science, Princeton University.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/blog/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>History of the Intro COS Lab</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/history-of-the-intro-cos-lab/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/history-of-the-intro-cos-lab/</guid><description>History of the Intro COS Lab</description></item><item><title>Introducing Brett and Giao, the 2023 Head Intro Lab Team!</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/introducing-brett-and-giao-the-2023-head-intro-lab-team/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/introducing-brett-and-giao-the-2023-head-intro-lab-team/</guid><description>Brett Zeligson &amp;lsquo;24, Head Intro Lab TA Tell us a bit about yourself, and what you have been doing at Princeton? Tell us a bit about yourself, and what you have been doing at Princeton? I’m a Junior majoring in Computer Science (BSE) pursuing certificates in Urban Studies, Finance, and Architecture/Engineering from West Orange, New Jersey. At Princeton, I’m involved in several student organizations including serving as an Advising Fellow for Matriculate, Head Web Design/Development Editor for The Daily Princetonian, and member of the Princeton Club Swim Team.</description></item><item><title>Diana Espindola and Austin Li talk about their experiences as Head Intro Lab Team in 2022</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/diana-espindola-and-austin-li-talk-about-their-experiences-as-head-intro-lab-team-in-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/diana-espindola-and-austin-li-talk-about-their-experiences-as-head-intro-lab-team-in-2022/</guid><description>Diana Espindola &amp;lsquo;23, Head Intro Lab TA Tell us a bit about yourself, and what you have been doing at Princeton and what you plan to do afterwards Why did you apply to be part of the Head Intro Lab Team? What are your takeaways from having served in 2022? What were the challenges you were proudest to overcome? Austin Li &amp;lsquo;23, Assistant Head Intro Lab TA Tell us a bit about yourself, and what you have been doing at Princeton and what you plan to do afterwards I&amp;rsquo;m a 2023 BSE COS major from Lexington, Kentucky.</description></item></channel></rss>