<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Intro COS Lab</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/</link><description>Recent content on Intro COS Lab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2022, Department of Computer Science, Princeton University.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Responsibilities of the Intro COS Lab Head Team</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-head-team/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-head-team/</guid><description>Once a semester:
interview Lab TAs hire interviewers schedule interviews go through TigerUHR applications and select students to interview; students can list if 126 Lab TA or 226/217 Lab TA is one of their most preferred note that for returning Lab TAs, we don&amp;rsquo;t reinterview; just check their attendance from last semester and make a decision create interview questions usually use an assignment and add some bugs to it for 126, there is just a 126 debugging; takes about 30 minutes for 226/217, there is a 226 debugging, 217 debugging, 226 conceptual, 217 conceptual question; takes about 45 minutes, probably give 1 hour to be safe use rubric hire lab TAs hire on TigerUHR 126: probably need around 25 full time 226/217: probably need around 30-35 full time a few subs for each is good schedule shifts use scheduling tool; some manual adjustment may be necessary afterwards things to keep in mind: 126 assignments are due Sunday, 226 assignments are due Monday, 217 assignments are due Tuesday/Thursday (check course website for exact schedule) train new Intro Lab TAs add new Intro Lab TAs to the Slack During the semester:</description></item><item><title>Information about Becoming an Intro Lab TA</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/information-about-becoming-an-intro-lab-ta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/information-about-becoming-an-intro-lab-ta/</guid><description>As part of the Intro Lab TA application process, candidates must complete an interview. Visit this page to learn more about the interview process.
You can also learn about all the other Undergraduate Course Assistant (UCA) positions in the Department of Computer Science.
Why would you want to be a lab TA? It&amp;rsquo;s rewarding to help people! Yaaay! It&amp;rsquo;s fun to help people with COS! Yaaay! You get lots and lots and lots of debugging experience!</description></item><item><title>How to use the Sub/Swap marketplace</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/how-to-use-the-sub/swap-marketplace/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/how-to-use-the-sub/swap-marketplace/</guid><description>Overview The sub/swap platform was designed to make requesting shift covers fairer, fulfill more requests, and increase transparency. It provides an online marketplace where students can buy-out of attending their shifts using virtual currency. Prices are determined by the amount of notice given, thus incentivizing students to post their requests as early as possible. By using the platform, users no longer need to go through the hassle of finding someone to cover their shift or swapping shifts with someone else after posting their request.</description></item><item><title>Peer Tutoring Guidelines for COS 126, 226 &amp; 217</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/peer-tutoring-guidelines-for-cos-126-226-217/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/peer-tutoring-guidelines-for-cos-126-226-217/</guid><description>Last revised: October 3, 2022, originally from here.
Congratulations on becoming a peer tutor! Please confirm that you understand these guidelines before you start tutoring by completing this affirmation form.
As a peer tutor, you have permission to look at the code of the person you are tutoring. It&amp;rsquo;s important, however, that you avoid looking at your own solutions while tutoring. That could inadvertently influence you to guide your student to a solution that would be so close to your old code that it would be flagged by the plagiarism software.</description></item><item><title>FAQ for TAs staffing the Intro Lab</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/faq-for-tas-staffing-the-intro-lab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/faq-for-tas-staffing-the-intro-lab/</guid><description>Before going through the questions, consider how we encourage students to interact with the Intro COS Lab.
General</description></item><item><title>History of the Intro COS Lab</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/history-of-the-intro-cos-lab/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/history-of-the-intro-cos-lab/</guid><description>History of the Intro COS Lab</description></item><item><title>Guide and Best Practices for GDB</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/guide-and-best-practices-for-gdb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/guide-and-best-practices-for-gdb/</guid><description>Note: This is not meant to be a comprehensive tutorial on how to use gdb, but rather a refresher on what you might encounter while helping 217 students debug and common commands you might have to use.
Part 1: How do I run gdb? Step 1: Make sure you build your program with -g.
Example: $ gcc217 -g test.c definitions.c -o testprgm
Step 2: Run gdb within emacs. Launch emacs: $ emacs Call gdb with these keystrokes: x gdb The editor should display a message like this:</description></item><item><title>Introducing Brett and Giao, the 2023 Head Intro Lab Team!</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/introducing-brett-and-giao-the-2023-head-intro-lab-team/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/introducing-brett-and-giao-the-2023-head-intro-lab-team/</guid><description>Brett Zeligson &amp;lsquo;24, Head Intro Lab TA Tell us a bit about yourself, and what you have been doing at Princeton? I’m a Junior majoring in Computer Science (BSE) pursuing certificates in Urban Studies, Finance, and Architecture/Engineering from West Orange, New Jersey. At Princeton, I’m involved in several student organizations including serving as an Advising Fellow for Matriculate, Head Web Design/Development Editor for The Daily Princetonian, and member of the Princeton Club Swim Team.</description></item><item><title>Responsibilities of the Intro COS Lab Interviewers</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-interviewers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-interviewers/</guid><description>Prior to interviews:
Familiarize yourself with the debugging question. Claim interview time slots. During interviews:
Introduce yourself. This includes name, year, major, and involvement with the IntroLab. Verify eligibility. Please confirm the position that the interview is for and whether the candidate meets the basic criteria to continue. (Ex: Completed COS 226 + 217 for 2xx Lab TA position) Brief summary of role. Explain that the purpose of Lab TAs is to help debug and teach students how to debug, NOT explain how to approach assignment or give conceptual explanations.</description></item><item><title>Diana Espindola and Austin Li talk about their experiences as Head Intro Lab Team in 2022</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/diana-espindola-and-austin-li-talk-about-their-experiences-as-head-intro-lab-team-in-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/diana-espindola-and-austin-li-talk-about-their-experiences-as-head-intro-lab-team-in-2022/</guid><description>Diana Espindola &amp;lsquo;23, Head Intro Lab TA Tell us a bit about yourself, and what you have been doing at Princeton and what you plan to do afterwards I am a senior studying computer science that hails from Miami, FL. During my time at Princeton I have gotten involved with the Entrepreneurship Club, Whitman College Council, Scholars Institute Fellows Program, and Princeton Student Agencies. After graduation I will join Microsoft as a program manager to gain real-world experience prior to attending business school.</description></item><item><title>Guide for Intro Lab TAs</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/guide-for-intro-lab-tas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/guide-for-intro-lab-tas/</guid><description>Once a semester:
Apply for either 126 or 2xx Lab TA position if you are a returning application, you do not need to interview again note that if you are a 126 Lab TA and wish to become a 2xx Lab TA, you will have to apply again. Make sure you are on payroll and in the slack channel Fill out your shift preferences Begin your shifts! Every shift:
Open labqueue.</description></item><item><title>How to Use Labqueue Password</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/how-to-use-labqueue-password/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/how-to-use-labqueue-password/</guid><description>COS 109, 126, 226, and 217 students, With Princeton coming out of the shadow of COVID, we wish to reimplement an in-person experience for students seeking help from Intro Lab TA&amp;rsquo;s. In order to make sure that students are in-person, we have added a password for attempting to join the labqueue. The password is randomized every day and seeks to ensure you are actually physically in the Intro Lab before adding yourself to the queue.</description></item><item><title>How to Effectively Use Intro Lab TAs</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/how-to-effectively-use-intro-lab-tas/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/how-to-effectively-use-intro-lab-tas/</guid><description>Dear COS 109, 126, 226, and 217 students, To help students get the most out of their interactions with Lab TAs, we have been working with the various course staff to clarify our guidelines. Before putting yourself on the queue, please make sure you have:
Identified a specific problem (e.g., instead of asking “is this correct?” ask &amp;ldquo;I am concerned that this will not work with large files but I am not sure how to test that&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;I am not certain my code meets the performance requirements because it takes a long time.</description></item><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>