<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>job-description on Intro COS Lab</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/blog/job-description/</link><description>Recent content in job-description on Intro COS Lab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2022, Department of Computer Science, Princeton University.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/blog/job-description/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guide for Intro Lab TAs</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/guide-for-intro-lab-tas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/guide-for-intro-lab-tas/</guid><description>Once a semester:
Apply for either 126 or 2xx Lab TA position if you are a returning application, you do not need to interview again note that if you are a 126 Lab TA and wish to become a 2xx Lab TA, you will have to apply again. Make sure you are on payroll and in the slack channel Fill out your shift preferences Begin your shifts! Every shift:
Open labqueue.</description></item><item><title>Responsibilities of the Intro COS Lab Interviewers</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-interviewers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-interviewers/</guid><description>This page is currently empty.</description></item><item><title>Responsibilities of the Intro COS Lab Head Team</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-head-team/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-head-team/</guid><description>Once a semester:
interview Lab TAs hire interviewers schedule interviews go through TigerUHR applications and select students to interview; students can list if 126 Lab TA or 226/217 Lab TA is one of their most preferred note that for returning Lab TAs, we don&amp;rsquo;t reinterview; just check their attendance from last semester and make a decision create interview questions usually use an assignment and add some bugs to it for 126, there is just a 126 debugging; takes about 30 minutes for 226/217, there is a 226 debugging, 217 debugging, 226 conceptual, 217 conceptual question; takes about 45 minutes, probably give 1 hour to be safe use rubric hire lab TAs hire on TigerUHR 126: probably need around 25 full time 226/217: probably need around 30-35 full time a few subs for each is good schedule shifts use scheduling tool; some manual adjustment may be necessary afterwards things to keep in mind: 126 assignments are due Sunday, 226 assignments are due Monday, 217 assignments are due Tuesday/Thursday (check course website for exact schedule) train new Intro Lab TAs add new Intro Lab TAs to the Slack During the semester:</description></item></channel></rss>