<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>job-description on Intro COS Lab</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/blog/job-description/</link><description>Recent content in job-description on Intro COS Lab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2022, Department of Computer Science, Princeton University.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/blog/job-description/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Responsibilities of the Intro COS Lab Interviewers</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-interviewers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-interviewers/</guid><description>Prior to interviews:
Familiarize yourself with the debugging question. Claim interview time slots. During interviews:
Introduce yourself. This includes name, year, major, and involvement with the IntroLab. Verify eligibility. Please confirm the position that the interview is for and whether the candidate meets the basic criteria to continue. (Ex: Completed COS 226 + 217 for 2xx Lab TA position) Brief summary of role. Explain that the purpose of Lab TAs is to help debug and teach students how to debug, NOT explain how to approach assignment or give conceptual explanations.</description></item><item><title>Guide for Intro Lab TAs</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/guide-for-intro-lab-tas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/guide-for-intro-lab-tas/</guid><description>Once a semester:
Apply for either 126 or 2xx Lab TA position if you are a returning application, you do not need to interview again note that if you are a 126 Lab TA and wish to become a 2xx Lab TA, you will have to apply again. Make sure you are on payroll and in the slack channel Fill out your shift preferences Begin your shifts! Every shift:
Open labqueue.</description></item><item><title>Responsibilities of the Intro COS Lab Head Team</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-head-team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-head-team/</guid><description>Once a semester:
Interview Lab TAs Hire interviewers Schedule interviews Go through TigerUHR applications and select students to interview; students can list if 126 Lab TA or 226/217 Lab TA is one of their most preferred Note that for returning Lab TAs, we don&amp;rsquo;t reinterview; just check their attendance from last semester and make a decision Create interview questions Usually use an assignment and add some bugs to it The COS 126 interview consists of a COS 126 debugging questions and takes about 30 minutes The COS 226/217 interview consists of a COS 226 debugging, COS 217 debugging, COS 226 conceptual, and COS 217 conceptual question.</description></item></channel></rss>