<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Intro CS Lab</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Intro CS Lab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2022, Department of Computer Science, Princeton University.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Effectively Use Intro Lab TAs</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/how-to-effectively-use-intro-lab-tas/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/how-to-effectively-use-intro-lab-tas/</guid><description>How to Effectively Use Lab TAs Dear COS 109, 126, 226, and 217 students, To help students get the most out of their interactions with Lab TAs, we have been working with the various course staff to clarify our guidelines. Before putting yourself on the queue, please make sure you have:
*Identified a specific problem (e.g., instead of asking “is this correct?” ask &amp;ldquo;I am concerned that this will not work with large files but I am not sure how to test that&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;I am not certain my code meets the performance requirements because it takes a long time.</description></item><item><title>Information for those who want to be an INTRO LAB TA!</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/information-for-those-who-want-to-be-an-intro-lab-ta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/information-for-those-who-want-to-be-an-intro-lab-ta/</guid><description>Why would you want to be a lab TA? It&amp;rsquo;s rewarding to help people! Yaaay! It&amp;rsquo;s fun to help people with COS! Yaaay! You get lots and lots and lots of debugging experience! You get paid! You really get to know the 126 &amp;amp; 226 &amp;amp; 217 material! You get to see how other people approach the assignments that you have once done&amp;hellip;which is always an interesting idea&amp;hellip; Requirements? The only official requirements are that you have completed COS 126 (for COS126 lab TAs) or COS 226 and COS 217 (for COS226/217 lab TAs).</description></item><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>