<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Intro COS Lab</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Intro COS Lab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2022, Department of Computer Science, Princeton University.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Information about Becoming an Intro Lab TA</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/information-about-becoming-an-intro-lab-ta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/information-about-becoming-an-intro-lab-ta/</guid><description>If you want to be notified when Spring 2023 applications will open, [https://ugradjobs.cs.princeton.edu/posts/2022-12-02-recruiting-ucas-for-spring-2023/](submit a notice of interest here)! We&amp;rsquo;ll be in touch when hiring opens in mid-January 2023.
Why would you want to be a lab TA? It&amp;rsquo;s rewarding to help people! Yaaay! It&amp;rsquo;s fun to help people with COS! Yaaay! You get lots and lots and lots of debugging experience! You get paid! You really get to know the 126 &amp;amp; 226 &amp;amp; 217 material!</description></item><item><title>Responsibilities of the Intro COS Lab Interviewers</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-interviewers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-interviewers/</guid><description>This page is currently empty.</description></item><item><title>Responsibilities of the Intro COS Lab Head Team</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-head-team/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-head-team/</guid><description>Once a semester:
interview Lab TAs hire interviewers schedule interviews go through TigerUHR applications and select students to interview; students can list if 126 Lab TA or 226/217 Lab TA is one of their most preferred note that for returning Lab TAs, we don&amp;rsquo;t reinterview; just check their attendance from last semester and make a decision create interview questions usually use an assignment and add some bugs to it for 126, there is just a 126 debugging; takes about 30 minutes for 226/217, there is a 226 debugging, 217 debugging, 226 conceptual, 217 conceptual question; takes about 45 minutes, probably give 1 hour to be safe use rubric hire lab TAs hire on TigerUHR 126: probably need around 25 full time 226/217: probably need around 30-35 full time a few subs for each is good schedule shifts use scheduling tool; some manual adjustment may be necessary afterwards things to keep in mind: 126 assignments are due Sunday, 226 assignments are due Monday, 217 assignments are due Tuesday/Thursday (check course website for exact schedule) train new Intro Lab TAs add new Intro Lab TAs to the Slack During the semester:</description></item><item><title>How to Use Labqueue Password</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/how-to-use-labqueue-password/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/how-to-use-labqueue-password/</guid><description>COS 109, 126, 226, and 217 students, With Princeton coming out of the shadow of COVID, we wish to reimplement an in-person experience for students seeking help from Intro Lab TA&amp;rsquo;s. In order to make sure that students are in-person, we have added a password for attempting to join the labqueue. The password is randomized every day and seeks to ensure you are actually physically in the Intro Lab before adding yourself to the queue.</description></item><item><title>How to Effectively Use Intro Lab TAs</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/how-to-effectively-use-intro-lab-tas/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/how-to-effectively-use-intro-lab-tas/</guid><description>Dear COS 109, 126, 226, and 217 students, To help students get the most out of their interactions with Lab TAs, we have been working with the various course staff to clarify our guidelines. Before putting yourself on the queue, please make sure you have:
Identified a specific problem (e.g., instead of asking “is this correct?” ask &amp;ldquo;I am concerned that this will not work with large files but I am not sure how to test that&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;I am not certain my code meets the performance requirements because it takes a long time.</description></item><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>