<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>head-team on Intro COS Lab</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/blog/head-team/</link><description>Recent content in head-team on Intro COS Lab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2022, Department of Computer Science, Princeton University.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/blog/head-team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing Brett and Giao, the 2023 Head Intro Lab Team!</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/introducing-brett-and-giao-the-2023-head-intro-lab-team/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/introducing-brett-and-giao-the-2023-head-intro-lab-team/</guid><description>Brett Zeligson &amp;lsquo;24, Head Intro Lab TA Tell us a bit about yourself, and what you have been doing at Princeton? I’m a Junior majoring in Computer Science (BSE) pursuing certificates in Urban Studies, Finance, and Architecture/Engineering from West Orange, New Jersey. At Princeton, I’m involved in several student organizations including serving as an Advising Fellow for Matriculate, Head Web Design/Development Editor for The Daily Princetonian, and member of the Princeton Club Swim Team.</description></item><item><title>Diana Espindola and Austin Li talk about their experiences as Head Intro Lab Team in 2022</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/diana-espindola-and-austin-li-talk-about-their-experiences-as-head-intro-lab-team-in-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/diana-espindola-and-austin-li-talk-about-their-experiences-as-head-intro-lab-team-in-2022/</guid><description>Diana Espindola &amp;lsquo;23, Head Intro Lab TA Tell us a bit about yourself, and what you have been doing at Princeton and what you plan to do afterwards Why did you apply to be part of the Head Intro Lab Team? What are your takeaways from having served in 2022? What were the challenges you were proudest to overcome? Austin Li &amp;lsquo;23, Assistant Head Intro Lab TA Tell us a bit about yourself, and what you have been doing at Princeton and what you plan to do afterwards I&amp;rsquo;m a 2023 BSE COS major from Lexington, Kentucky.</description></item><item><title>Responsibilities of the Intro COS Lab Head Team</title><link>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-head-team/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://introlab.cs.princeton.edu/responsibilities-of-the-intro-cos-lab-head-team/</guid><description>Once a semester:
interview Lab TAs hire interviewers schedule interviews go through TigerUHR applications and select students to interview; students can list if 126 Lab TA or 226/217 Lab TA is one of their most preferred note that for returning Lab TAs, we don&amp;rsquo;t reinterview; just check their attendance from last semester and make a decision create interview questions usually use an assignment and add some bugs to it for 126, there is just a 126 debugging; takes about 30 minutes for 226/217, there is a 226 debugging, 217 debugging, 226 conceptual, 217 conceptual question; takes about 45 minutes, probably give 1 hour to be safe use rubric hire lab TAs hire on TigerUHR 126: probably need around 25 full time 226/217: probably need around 30-35 full time a few subs for each is good schedule shifts use scheduling tool; some manual adjustment may be necessary afterwards things to keep in mind: 126 assignments are due Sunday, 226 assignments are due Monday, 217 assignments are due Tuesday/Thursday (check course website for exact schedule) train new Intro Lab TAs add new Intro Lab TAs to the Slack During the semester:</description></item></channel></rss>